A New Wave of Horror
Dark Waters is a horror, mystery film directed by Mariano Baino.
After the death of her father, a young woman travels to a remote convent on an
island in the Black Sea to find out why her father funded it for years.
Elizabeth, played by Louise Kim Salter.
Sarah, played by Venera Simmons.
Mother Superior, played by Mariya Kapnist.
Mother Superior's Assistant, played by Lubov Snegur.
Old Blind Woman, played by Albina Skarga.
Fisherman, played by Valeriy Bassel.
Dark Waters (also known as Dead Waters in the American home-video edition), is a 1993 horror film
directed by Mariano Baino, who co-wrote it with Andy Bark and also served as the editor.
The film explores themes of mother, monster, nun, knife, talisman.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.